flcourts.org 2006-06-15

# Privacy Policy

Internet Privacy Policy

_T_ hank you for visiting the Florida State Courts Web site. Your privacy is very important to the Office of the State Courts Administrator. It is the policy of the judicial branch to collect no personal information about you when you visit www.flcourts.org, unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available. 

When you visit www.flcourts.org, the Web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed the site. This information does not capture or identify your personal e-mail address or other personal information. 

In addition, information is only gathered regarding the volume and timing of access to the site by collecting information on the date, time and pages you visited while at the site. This is done so that the content of the site can be improved. Your personal information is not identified through this data collection process. 

If you choose to share personal information, such as by sending a message or filling out an electronic form with personal information, the information will be saved for a designated period of time in order to comply with Judicial Branch public records retention policies. However, information will not be disclosed to third parties or other government agencies, unless required by state or federal law. Please note that Florida's public records law requires that information received in connection with court business must be made available to anyone upon request, unless the information is subject to a specific exemption. 

If you have other questions about this privacy policy, or have suggestions on how it may be improved, please feel free to contact us.
